Hello, mummy.
嗨，妈妈
How are you, son?
怎么样，儿子？
I am good.
我很好
How are studies going?
学习进展如何？
It's going well.
一切都很顺利
Classes have begun.
已经开始上课了
His routine will be disturbed.
他的作息时间都乱套了
Let him sleep.
让他睡觉吧
You let the day pass and then call specifically at night.
白天那么长时间你不打电话，非要等晚上才打
Tell me.
告诉我
Are you in good spirit?
你心情怎么样？
Yes, mummy.
还挺好的
How do you manage to keep repeating the same question?
这个问题你已经问了无数次了
Okay.
好吧
I'll hang up then.
那我就挂了
- Goodnight. - Goodnight.
- 晚安-晚安
Are you revising 'coordinate' inside?
你是在里面改坐标吗？
Just two more minutes, bro.
再给我点时间，兄弟
Did it fall?
它会掉下来对吧？
Did I tell you or not?
早就告诉过你们
Jeetu Bhaiya and Physics can never be wrong.
杰图·拜亚和物理学永远不会出错
Bhaiya. Bhaiya. Once more.
拜亚哥，再来一次
How many times did you pay the fees?
你交了几次的钱？
What if I say 'once more'?
我要是让你再交一次钱呢？
Look at that. He is feeling sleepy in class.
看，他在课堂上犯困了
Am I that boring?
我有那么无聊吗？
I stole someone's wheel at 4:30 AM.
我凌晨4:30偷了别人的车
He may show up anytime.
他随时都可能来找我
And this chap is all sleepy.
然而这家伙居然困了
Sorry, sir.
对不起，老师
- I could not sleep all night, so.. - What did you just say? Come again?
- 我整晚都睡不着，所以...-你刚才说什么? 再说一遍？
- I could not sleep all night.. - No. No. Before that?
- 我整晚都睡不着...-不是这句，再往前一句
Sorry, sir.
对不起，老师
Sir!
老师！
Did everyone hear that?
大家都听到了吗？
Sir.
他管我叫老师
Jeetu Bhaiya is no longer a 'Bhaiya' (brother).
杰图·拜亚已经不是拜亚哥了
What am I now?
我现在是什么？
Sir!
老师！
Batla sir and Rao sir aren't the only sirs.
不是只有巴特拉和饶才能叫老师
Even Jeetu Bhaiya is now a..
现在我也能称什么……
Sir!
老师！
You surely deserve a prize.
来，我应该给你点奖励
- Come over. - Go. Go
- 过来-快去
- Come. - Well done!
- 来吧-干得漂亮
The credit for my success goes to my mother Mrs.
我的成功要归功于我母亲
Sumitra..
苏米特拉
Scoot! Go and wash your face. Go!
快去! 去洗洗脸，快去！
He wants to take my hard earned money.
他想拿走我辛辛苦苦挣来的钱
- You are so dramatic, Bhaiya. - Why shouldn't I be?
- 你翻脸太快了，拜亚哥 -有什么问题吗？
I wasn't the Governor of Dramatics society IIT Kharagpur for nothing.
我这个哈拉格布尔戏剧协会的总管可不是白当的
Let's resume.
让我们继续
- A beautiful damsel. - Yes, sir.
-话说有一个漂亮小姐姐 -好的，老师
Yes! Now you're all awake.. at the mention of 'damsel'.
一说到小姐姐你们就都精神了
- Are the patties fresh, brother? - Certainly.
- 馅饼新鲜吗?-当然
Give me one.
给我来一个
You are foregoing food for patties?
你怎么不吃饭，吃馅饼？
It is not food. It is bullcrap!
这哪是饭，这是垃圾！
Just a week away from home and you've turned foul-mouthed.
离家才一个星期你就满嘴脏话了
Bullcrap is not a cuss word.
垃圾又不是脏话
It's a body product.
你就把这当作是身体的必需品
Fertilizer.
肥料
Agarwal sir used to utter it even in classroom.
阿加瓦尔先生曾经在课堂上也说这个词
Give me pickle.
给我来点泡菜
Carry on.
你们继续
Uday, rather than learning hard work, discipline..
乌代，阿加瓦尔先生课上还说要刻苦学习、高度自律
..and punctuality, you choose to learn cuss words from Agarwal sir.
你怎么就不学点好的
And you... Munching patties all the time.
还有你...都吃好几天馅饼了
You'll grow weaker if you skip meals.
如果你再不好好吃饭，肯定会变得更虚弱
If you grow weak you fall ill.
如果你变得虚弱，你就会生病
And the children who fall ill within the first week..
第一周内生病的孩子
..are taken back home by their parents.
会被父母带回家
And they never make it to IIT.
从此与印度理工无缘
Meena, I will fall ill even if I eat this food.
米纳，我就算吃了这些东西，我也会生病的
This is so oily.
这菜太油腻了
- Is oil free or what? - Speak softly.
-这是把卖油的打死了吧?-小声点
If Chandru hears then we'll get mixed vegetables of all the gourds for dinner.
如果被钱德鲁听到，我们晚餐就只能吃拌蔬菜了
Including bitter gourd.
里面还有苦瓜
Still drinking Bisleri?
你还喝上酒了？
Meena. Not Bisleri. Aquafina.
米纳，这是百岁山，不是牛栏山
It's all the Bisleri's are the same.
都差不多
Why are you squandering money? Drink this.
你为什么要浪费钱喝这么贵的水？
The mess does not make the water.
水是无辜的
My thirst doesn't get quenched by this water.
这的水都不解渴
It is salty.
还有点咸
- The Chambal water.. Is hard. - Is hard.
- 昌巴尔的水质... 很硬-很硬
I know.
我知道
I've been hearing this for the past week.
过去一周我都听到无数次了
Look, if you don't eat well you won't be able to concentrate.
听着，如果你吃得不好，你就不能集中注意力
Then you won't be able to study long.
这样你就不能长时间学习了
As it is you are facing so many complexities why invite a new one.
你现在的问题已经够多了，为什么还要自找麻烦
Look, if you drink more of this you will spend more money..
听着，如果你一直喝这个，你就会浪费很多钱
..if you drink less you will be constipated.
如果水喝的少，你就会便秘
I already am.
我已经便秘了
You couldn't empty your bowels even today?
你今天还是没拉出来吗？
What kind of conversation is this for the dining table?
兄弟，我这吃饭呢，聊这个合适吗？
Wonderful! When you called this delicious food a body product..
你刚才不是还说饭是身体的肥料
..was the conversation good then!?
你怎么不考虑合适不合适？
You couldn't empty your bowels?
还是拉不出来吗？
Are you going empty it for him?
你要帮他拉吗？
Uday!
乌代！
Let's go for some tea.
我们去喝点茶吧
Come. Oh, Shivangi!
来吧，宝贝！
You bite so hard.
你咬得太狠了
Raunchy!
调皮！
Meena.
米纳
Let's go for a tea.
我们去喝杯茶吧
It isn't 5:30 as yet.
现在还不到5:30
Have you finished the sheet?
你做完这套题了吗？
Yes, I've completed up to 35.
是的，我做到第35题了
You completed 35?
你完成了35个？
You did it very fast. I am still on the 30th.
你做得好快，我还在做第30题
Why don't you complete it? It will be done by 5:30.
你怎么不一口气做完呢?五点半之前要做完
How do you guys manage to sit for so long?
你们怎么能坐这么久？
I get tired in a little while.
我坐一会就累了
Don't say that.
别这么说
Even yesterday you didn't finish the homework.
昨天你作业都没做完
If you leave it today as well, it's bound to pile up.
如果你今天也不做完，那一定会越积越多
I am not up to it.
我做不到
Then try to read the theory. Utilize your time.
好好思考一下怎么合理利用时间
I don't feel like it now.
我现在不想思考
This is what I've been trying to explain to you for so long.
这就是我一直想跟你说的
You know what.
你知道吗
Read Flamingo for now.
读读《火烈鸟》
It's a light read and will prepare you for boards too.
这是一本轻松的读物，能让为你为考试做好准备
Take it.
拿着
It contains stories.
里面有很多故事
A monkey is pulling down an object through a pulley.
一只猴子正在通过滑轮拉下一个物体
Another monkey is pulling the first monkey's tail.
另一只猴子正在拉第一只猴子的尾巴
Since it is pulling his tail it is bound to create tension.
因为它在拉它的尾巴，所以必然会产生紧张的气氛
Vaibhav!
瓦伊巴夫！
Your symptoms do not appear right to me at all.
你的状态在我看来完全不对劲
You need the guidance of someone wise.
你需要一个聪明人的指导
- Who? - A counselor.
- 谁?-心理咨询师
Psychiatrist?
心理医生？
Counselor? Like hell!
咨询师? 见鬼去吧！
Is this a mental problem? Am I depressed?
我是精神病吗? 我抑郁吗？
Do I have anxiety? Am I suicidal?
我有焦虑症吗? 我有自杀倾向吗？
Have I lost my mind that I need a counselor?
我看起来像是个需要看心理医生的人吗？
And anyways, half the counselors here are frauds.
不管怎样，这里一多半的咨询师都是骗子
I don't need anybody.
我才不需要咨询师
You need Alprozolam, which is good for your sleep..
你需要阿普唑仑，能提升你的睡眠质量
..and can restore the balance of serotonin and dopamine in your body.
可以恢复你体内血清素和多巴胺的平衡
And Lactulose for your constipation problems.
乳果糖可以缓解你的便秘问题
Pay the fees outside.
门口交费
You do know that you are not a Doctor, right?
你知道你不是医生吧？
Just because I wore a coat instead of an apron..
就因为我穿的实验服而不是白大褂
..and my handwriting is not good, does it mean I am not a Doctor?
还有我的字写得不好，就能说明我不是医生吗？
Because you don't have a license.
因为你没有执照
Why have you worn this lab coat?
你为什么穿着这件实验服？
Don't dress for the job you have.
穿什么
Dress for the job you want.
就是什么
Vaibhav.
瓦伊巴夫
I know what you need.
我知道你需要什么了
Radha Krishna temple.
克利须那神庙
All your prayers are answered over here.
神会听到你的许愿
Take this.
拿着这个
Write it nicely with a clean heart.
用你最真诚的心写下你的愿望
It is mathematically impossible, Meena.
从数学的角度来讲这是不可能的，米纳
There aren't as many seats in IIT as the number of prayers here.
印度理工学院的座位远不如来这许愿的人多
What is this, Meena?
搞毛线啊，米纳？
Why did you have to bring us here?
你为什么要把我们带到这里来？
Help me.
上帝保佑
Are you crazy?
你疯了吗？
It was needed.
这是很有必要的
But not from anybody. A loved one.
来自一个所爱的人，而不是外人
Someone who would empathize. Someone who has faced this himself.
一个能够感同身受的人，一个亲身经历过这一切的人
So, he told me about you. That's why I brought him here.
他跟我说起过你，所以我才带他来这儿
Did the right thing, didn't I?
我来对地方了，不是吗？
Absolutely.
当然
You certainly are wise.
你确实很聪明
Ofcouse, he is in Maheshwari.
当然了，他在马赫什瓦里教育
Piyush.
皮尤什
You tell me how you managed, bro.
快告诉我你是怎么做到的，兄弟
My food, drink, potty and sleep, everything is out of order.
我现在吃不好，睡不好，还便秘
How did you get my address?
你怎么知道我的地址的？
From your parents..
从你的父母那里
..because you weren't answering my phone.
因为你不接我电话
Smart, right?
很聪明，对吧？
Again, my idea.
这也是我的主意
Very nice.
非常好
I won't take up much of your time.
我不会占用你太多时间
I understand the pressure from Maheshwari.
我能理解马赫什瓦里压力很大
Just share with me any coping mechanism.
跟我分享一下你的应对机制吧
I am not able to handle it.
我实在受不了了
A friend in need is a friend indeed, right?
患难见真情，对吧？
Isn't that right, brother?
对吧，兄弟？
You did the right thing coming here?
你真是来对地方了
Ain't that true?
难道不是吗？
Thank you.
谢谢你
You did the right thing..
太对了
..because even I am unable to handle it.
因为我也受不了了
It seems even Piyush is constipated.
看来皮尤什也便秘了
This is something else, Meena.
不是一回事，兄弟
What's the matter, bro?
怎么了，兄弟？
I am not in Maheshwari.
我不在马赫什瓦里
I've been taking individual lessons for the past six months.
在过去的六个月里，我一直在上私教
My suspicion turned out right, Meena.
我的猜测是对的，米纳
Didn't I tell you,
我跟你说过
what is a 'Maheshwari' boy doing in Talwandi instead of Vigyan Nagar.
为什么一个‘马赫什瓦里’的学生会住在塔万迪萨博，而不是维根纳加尔
I don't understand.
我不明白
What are you saying?
你在说什么？
Dad got me admitted using influence..
我爸是托关系才给我送进马赫什瓦里的
..but when the batch was shuffled after the first test..
但是第一次考试之后我就被排到后面的分组了
..I ended up in the last batch.
最后一组
The next time I was the last student in that batch as well.
第二次考试我又是最后一组的倒数第一
Then I had to leave Maheshwari and opt for individual coaching.
然后我不得不退学，选择上私教
I see.
我明白了
That's why you wouldn't return my calls, you rascal.
这就是你不回我电话的原因，你这个无赖
- So sorry, brother. - Get lost!
- 对不起，兄弟 - 滚蛋
How could I tell you?
你要我怎么开口？
Dad has bragged all over Itarsi..
爸爸在老家到处吹嘘
..that I am in Maheshwari.
我在马赫什瓦里教育
Ya.
是啊
He does brag alot.
他确实爱吹牛
He told all of Itarsi that I didn't get admitted to Maheshwari.
他在老家跟所有人说我没被马赫什瓦里录取
All of Itarsi feels I will surely get admitted to IIT.
老家亲戚朋友都认为我一定能考上印度理工
Yes. All of us feel that way.
是的，我们都有这种感觉
Yes.
是的
I was baffled as to how he soared so suddenly.
我还很纳闷他的成绩是怎么突然飙上来的
I hope your family knows.
我希望你的家人知道
- No, buddy. - No?
- 不行，兄弟 - 不行？
Last time when I went home for Diwali..
上次我回家的时候
..I had planned on disclosing everything and end the matter but..
我本来打算把一切都说出来，结束这件事，但是……
But?
但是？
For the first time in my life Neha called.
这是我有生以来第一次接到尼哈打来的电话
Neha Purohit?
尼哈 · 普罗希特？
Yes. You know her younger sister.
是的，你认识她的妹妹
- Shilpa? - Yes.
- 希尔帕?-是的
She was thinking of IIT herself and needed tips from me.
她也想考印度理工学院，需要我的建议
So both of them came to my place.
所以他们两个都来了我家
Both Neha and Shilpa?
尼哈和希尔帕？
- Yes. - Their mom came too.
- 是的-还有他们的妈妈也来了
- Aunt Disha? - Yes.
- 迪莎阿姨?-是的
For the first time in my life I got so much recognition..
这是我有生以来第一次得到如此多的认可
..how could I have let it go?
我怎么能就这么算了呢？
Also, do you know, during the conversation..
还有，你知道吗，在谈话中
..aunt confirmed my time and date of birth.
阿姨还跟我确认了我的出生日期和时间
Even I am preparing for IIT.
我也在为印度理工学院做准备啊
I was a better student than you in school.
我在学校成绩还比你好
She never asked me for tips.
她怎么不来找我要建议
You are studying in Prodigy.
因为你在神童教育
Never mind all of that. Tell me what I should do.
先不说那些了，快帮我想想办法
You..
你啊
..better see a counselor.
最好去看看心理医生
Yes, mummy.
喂，妈妈
What were you doing?
你在干什么？
Nothing. Was studying when..
没什么，我在学习
..an idle lady disturbed me.
然后一位无所事事的女士打扰了我
How could she do that?
她怎么能这么做？
Make it clear to your landlady when you are studying she..
在你学习的时候你要跟你房东说清楚，不要来打扰……
I got it.
我知道了
I'll hang up. You continue studying.
我挂了，你继续学习吧
Are you in a good spirit?
你心情怎么样？
Yes, mummy. I am.
可好了，放心吧
Until I categorically tell you never assume otherwise.
除非我明确告诉你，否则就不要自己乱猜
Well, goodnight.
好吧，晚安
Goodnight.
晚安
What do you mean?
什么意思？
"I didn't attempt the problem as I didn't understand it."
“我没做这道题，因为我看不懂”
Always look for hints, so many are there.
一定要寻找线索，题干里面给出了很多线索
Where?
在哪呢？
The first hint is that the problem is given.
第一个提示就是这道题是人出的
When the maker has posed the problem to us..
当出题者向我们提出问题时
..that means it's solvable with our knowledge.
这就意味着利用我们现有的知识是可以解决的
Secondly the velocity is given.
另外速度也给了
See. Is it or isn't it?
看到了吧，是不是？
So, it will be used in either of the two things.
那么速度只有在两种情况下会用到
Energy or momentum.
能量或动量
Now you have to decide which gamble to take.
现在你要决定赌一把
If it still doesn't make sense then keep looking for hints.
如果你还是没看懂，那么继续寻找线索
Is the word 'friction' visible?
“摩擦”这个词看到了吗？
Yes.
是的
It means energy cannot be used.
这意味着不是能量
What does that leave? Conservation of momentum.
那还剩什么了? 动量守恒
Initial equal to final.
初始值等于最终值
Say yes or no.
回答是或不是
Yes, sir.
是的
Just equate initial to final.
只需要把初始值和最终值等同起来
Tick it and move on.
打勾然后看下一题
At some point in the future whilst laughing, singing..
在未来的某个时刻，可能在你开心的唱歌时
..or in toilet you will realize..
或者在上厕所时，你就会意识到
..why was the momentum conserved.
为什么动量是守恒的
Okay?
好吗？
Even if you don't understand the question jostle with it.
即使你不理解这个问题，你也要解题
What do you do?
你是做什么的？
Jostle with it.
解题的
Yes.
是的
Once you have learned to jostle with questions and twirl the pen...
一旦你学会了解题和转笔
..you are already half an IITian.
你就已经是半个理工学院人了
Come on. Next.
来吧下一题
Hello, bro. Didn't you do the rest?
你要去哪，剩下的题你不做了吗？
Sir, I only did up to number 52.
老师，我只做到了52题
I see. You completed 52. Very good!
我明白了，你做了52道题，非常棒！
It's me who hates the environment.
我这人就是不爱护环境
I made a 150 page long sheet just to waste paper, right?
我印150道题就是为了浪费纸，对吧？
Sir, Not that I can't crack problems..
不是我不能解题
..but I am unable to sit for long.
而是我坐不住板凳
I'm not in the right spirit.
我心情不好
Is this the problem or there's more to it?
这是真的吗，还是另有隐情？
Bhaiya, he doesn't even eat well.
拜亚哥，他来了之后吃不好
He survives on Maggi and patties.
他靠吃馅饼生存
He still drinks Bisleri water and doesn't even sleep.
他每天喝矿泉水，甚至都不怎么睡觉
Why, brother?
真的吗？
Yes, Bhaiya.
是的，拜亚哥
You came late.
你来的比别人晚
So he missed the orientation.
所以错过了迎新会
He does not know the two important concepts of living in Kota.
他不知道在科塔生活的两个重要概念
Tell him, Meenal.
告诉他，米娜尔
What are they?
两个什么概念？
Firstly, Jeetu Bhaiya is not our physics faculty.
首先，杰图·拜亚不是我们的物理教员
He is our agony aunt.
他是我们的知心姐姐
He solves all kinds of problems.
能解决各种各样的问题
Academic, non-academic, personal, financial or romantic.
学术问题，非学术问题，个人问题，经济问题或者感情问题
Even if your landlord has kicked you out of the house..
即使你半夜喝多了
..in the middle of the night or if you've argued with the mess people..
被房东赶出来
..or if a Policeman has caught you reading obscene literature.
或者是被警察抓到你看黄色杂志
Jeetu Bhaiya solves everything.
杰图·拜亚都能解决
Just call him immediately and Jeetu Bhaiya solves all the problems.
只要给他打电话，杰图·拜亚就能帮助你
And..
还有
..the second?
第二个？
You forgot the second?
你忘了第二个？
Yes.
是的
Every child is special.
"每个孩子都是特别的"
That is utter nonsense.
这完全是胡说八道
You are not some unique personality.
你不是什么独一无二的人
These problems occur to thousands of students each year.
你遇到的问题每年都会发生在成千上万的学生身上
Before preparing for IIT at Kota one must prepare themselves to live in Kota.
在准备去理工学院生活之前，你必须学会在科塔生存
And there are simple ways to do it.
有很多简单的方法可以做到
If you encounter problems..
如果你遇到问题
Jostle with them.
解决问题
Even if you don't like the water, Just drink it.
即使你不喜欢这里的水，也要喝
Even if you don't like the mess food, Just eat it.
即使你不喜欢这些乱七八糟的食物，也要吃
Even if you are unable to sit for long Just sit for long.
即使你不能长时间地坐着，也要一直坐着
Challenge yourself. I will sit for long.
挑战你自己，我会坐很久
I won't get up at all.
我根本起不来
I will solve problems. I will read theories.
我要解题，我要读书
I will watch Unacademy's lessons.
我要看讲座
I will go through old papers.
我要复习以前的错题
I will sleep, I will die but I won't get up.
我会睡觉，我会死，但我就是不会站起来
So, what have you done?
这样的话，你做到了什么？
You have turned your problems to dare.
你已经把你遇到的问题转化为勇气
And dare is directly connected to ego.
而勇气则与自我直接相关
Ego has many disadvantages but it has one advantage too.
自我有许多缺点，但它也有优点
Things seem to be doable.
事情似乎是可行的
And you don't have to do this drama for long.
你不必长时间强迫自己去做这些事情
How many days?
多少天？
21 days.
21天
You can form any or give up any habit in 21 days.
你可以在21天内养成或放弃任何习惯
I had a smoking problem.
我以前抽烟很凶
2 packs a day.
一天两包
I lost it.
我戒掉了
I left it one day and after that I bragged about it at home..
戒烟之后我就在家里炫耀
..to my girlfriend, faculty, driver and the driver's wife.
给我的女朋友，同事，司机和司机的妻子炫耀
So much so, I gave 2000 rupees to the vendor..
因此，我给了那个小贩2000卢比
..not to give me cigarettes to smoke.
不要把烟卖给我
If you brag about it to the world then the world won't let you smoke.
如果你向全世界吹嘘，那么世界就不会让你吸烟
I felt a little urge in the beginning and then some more.
刚开始戒烟的时候我很难受，很想抽烟
By the time 21 days had passed the urge was zero.
但是过了21天，这种欲望就没有了
That's what you have to do.
这就是你必须做的
Say something. Yes or no.
说点什么，是或不是
Yes, Bhaiya.
是的，拜亚哥
Uday is a nasty fella..
乌代是个讨厌的家伙
..but Meena, you knew this was happening with your friend..
但是米纳，你明知道你的朋友会这样
..and still didn't tell him?
但你还是没告诉他？
Bhaiya, I..
拜亚哥，我……
You too, Brutus.
你也一样，布鲁图斯
You too.
你也一样
Did you notice?
你注意到了吗？
Bhaiya called me Brutus. 'Brutus Meena'
拜亚哥叫我布鲁图斯，‘布鲁图斯·米纳’
What? Don't you have any sense of humour?
干嘛? 你没有一点幽默感吗？
I might look nasty but not from the heart.
我很丑，但是我很温柔
Sure, I'm a member of the Bihar Tigers.
当然，我是比哈尔猛虎的成员
I have the responsibility of the entire city on these shoulders.
我肩负着整个城市和平
But Uday Gupta never ignores his sidekicks.
但是乌代 · 古普塔绝不会忽视他的朋友
..because your brother is the king of the streets.
因为你哥我是街头之王
I have taken the annual subscription for Unacademy plus.
我已经开启了'非学术'的年度订阅
For you.
给你开的
Go. Attend as many live lectures as you wish.
去吧，想听多少讲座就听多少
And always remember. Your brother is Caesar, not Brutus.
永远记住，你的兄弟是我，不是布鲁图斯
This man rises up at 3 pm.
他下午三点才起床
But don't you rise. Go study.
但是你不要起来，去学习
What are you looking at? Go study.
你在看什么? 快去学习
One cannot hate what one does not see.
人不会讨厌他看不见的东西
Don't look at the mess food at all.
完全不要看那些乱七八糟的食物
Pick up bread without a fuss.
不慌不忙地撕一块面包
Dip it in whatever and just chew.
随便蘸点什么，嚼嚼就行了
Sometimes you may be tempted to look down..
有时你可能会忍不住下看
..but therein lies your defeat.
但这就是你的失败之处
Tastes even better today.
今天味道好多了
Don't drink water at room temperature.
不要喝常温的水
Drink chilled water of the fridge.
喝冰箱里的冷水
People even savour beer if chilled.
人们甚至觉得冰镇啤酒都好喝
Salt water is nothing.
盐水算不了什么
Bottoms up.
干杯
Here x is given as the distance of the block..
这里的 x 表示块的距离
..and we have to find the velocity as a function of x.
我们必须找到速度作为 x 的函数
Just choose the correct option.
只要选择正确的选项
C.
C.
When did you come?
你什么时候来的？
I came to check on you.
我来看看你
Good! Good!
很好! 很好！
If you have chosen C option then your answer is correct.
如果你选择了 c 选项，那么你的答案是正确的
Now I shall tell you the solution of this question.
现在我来告诉你这个问题的解决办法
Yes, I have eaten.
是的，我吃过了
I am all well and am in good spirits.
我很好，精神也很好
Mummy, how do you manage to keep repeating the same question everyday?
妈妈，你怎么能每天都问我同样的问题呢？
Okay.
好吧
Apply more pressure, bro.
再用点力，兄弟
Vaibhav.
瓦伊巴夫
Is it working?
有用吗？
Lentil soup, veggies and breads have to be prepared..
扁豆汤，蔬菜和面包都准备好
..so there is always a scope of mistake.
所以总会有一个错误范围
Given the scope, the cooks in the mess ensure mistakes.
在这样的范围内，厨师们肯定会犯错误
That's why one should prefer eating what they don't make..
这就是为什么一个人应该更喜欢吃自己不做的东西
..such as salad, pickle, papad, yogurt and sugar.
例如沙拉，泡菜，薄饼，酸奶和糖
And there is your three course meal.
这样你的套餐就做好了
I have helped many people crap.
我治好了很多人的便秘
Yours is no different.
你的也一样
Two puffs.
两口
Only two puffs.
只要两口
You will experience streamline motion.
你就能体验到飞一般的感觉
Not friction.
完全没有摩擦力
Nonsense.
胡说八道
Take it. This is 'the truth'. -Scram! Bloody addict!
-拿着，这是“真相”-滚开! 该死的瘾君子！
Children, today we shall solve a problem on vertical circular motion.
孩子们，今天我们要解决一个关于垂直圆周运动的问题
Let me first explain the problem to you.
让我先给你解释一下这个问题
Vaibhav.
瓦伊巴夫
Aunty.
房东阿姨
She was walking down the stairs and fell.
她走下楼梯时摔倒了
She is frothing in the mouth.
口吐白沫
Hello. Ambulance.
你好，我需要救护车
Come to Lal Burj quickly. It's an emergency.
快来拉尔 · 伯奇酒店，非常紧急
What? Froth? Where?
什么? 泡沫? 哪里？
You got up?
这就起来了？
For that two-bit woman?
为了那个老巫婆？
You just want an excuse.
你只是想找个理由站起来
Damn you!
去你的吧！
You will bring disgrace on us in Jeetu Bhaiya's presence.
你会在拜亚哥面前给我们带来耻辱
Give me my 100 rupees from the bet.
把赌注里的100卢比给我
Engineer.
工程师
Nature has done half the job.
大自然已经完成了一半的工作
Water contains salt.
水含有盐分
Just add salt and lemon to it.
只要加盐和柠檬就行了
Lemonade is ready.
这样柠檬水就做好了
This small tip saves ten million children's lives every year.
这个小知识每年拯救一千万儿童的生命
It's great!
太棒了！
Isn't it?
不是吗？
Go and prepare two glasses now.
现在去拿两个杯子
Three.
三个
Mummy, Uday's girlfriend does not call him as many times as you call me.
妈妈，乌代的女朋友给乌代打电话的次数，远没有你给我打电话的次数多
Go! Go! Go! Come on!
走! 走! 走! 快点！
Well done, bro! Well done!
干得好，兄弟! 干得好！
You are under the oath of IIT.
你就快进入印度理工了，加油
One can't follow one days, how will one follow test cricket?
如果连一天都坚持不下来，那还怎么看板球比赛？
The T-20 format has been created for Kota students.
T-20版本是专为科塔学生设计的
IPL is the future.
IPL（印度超级板球联赛）是未来的趋势
If only they would take Yuvraj to play.
要是他们能让尤弗拉伊上场就好了
It's very wrong of them.
那就大错特错了
You are correct, bro. It's all politics.
你说得对，兄弟，这都是政治手段
Bro, Yuvi can and Yuvi will.
兄弟，尤维可以，绝对行
That's right, bro. Yuvraj will return.
没错，兄弟，尤弗拉伊会回来的
You can quote me on that.
记住我说的话
You?
你觉得呢？
Yes.
是的
He will return.
他会回来的
Children, today we shall solve a problem on impulse momentum theorem
孩子们，今天我们要解决一个关于冲量动量定理的问题
In it we shall learn to calculate impulse.
在这节课中，我们将学习计算推动力
Wow! There was no sound today.
哇! 今天一点声音都没有
You know this is really inappropriate.
你知道你这样真的很变态吧
I'm happy for you, buddy.
我为你感到高兴，兄弟
Children, we will solve a problem on friction today.
孩子们，我们今天要解决一个关于摩擦力的问题
As you can see in the picture two blocks are made.
正如你在图片中看到的那样，有两个木块
Both the blocks are kept on a wedge
这两个木块都放在一个楔子上
..and both are connected with the help of a string.
两者都是用一根绳子连接起来的
[Educator speaking]
blah blah blah…
Shall we?
走吧？
It is 6:30 already.
已经六点半了
Let's go.
我们走
One step closer to IIT
贴近理工学院的一小步
That was done in class.
这些是在课堂上完成的
But I'm glad today you came with DPP and sheets finished.
但我很高兴你今天把作业做完了
That means this chap is able to sit up longer.
这就意味着你完全可以坐得更久
Yes, sir.
是的
Is food and water sorted?
饮食问题解决了吗？
Yes, Bhaiya.
是的，拜亚哥
Are you able to crap properly?
你能正常拉屎了吗？
Oh, Bhaiya!
哦，兄弟！
Come along. Why are you being shy with me?
来吧，你为什么对我这么害羞？
I am your agony aunt.
我是你的知心大姐
And we have a long journey together.
我们还有很长的路要走
Everyone has these problems.
每个人都会有这样那样的问题
I too have them.
我也有
Have you been doing Physical Chemistry?
你学过物理化学吗？
Give me one.
给我根烟
A cigarette?
香烟？
Yes.
是的
Cigarette, Bhaiya?
你不是戒烟了吗？
When I don't feel the urge and the situation is under control..
当我感受不到刺激，情况在我掌控之中的时候
..then you can cheat sometimes.
也是可以作弊的
Cheating occasionally is fine.
偶尔作弊是可以的
As long as it doesn't become a habit.
但不要经常作弊
- What's the matter? - Auto!
- 怎么了?-摩托车！
Lets rush to Vigyan Nagar.
赶紧去维根纳加尔
- Let's go, sir. - Bhaiya!
- 我们走，先生-拜亚哥！
- Bhaiya! - I'll see you later.
- 拜亚哥!-回头见
What happened?
发生了什么？
Nature's call?
大自然的召唤？
Yes.
是的
Meena.
米纳
Come.
来吧
It's only 5 O'clock.
现在才5点
Let's go! Come!
我们走! 快！
It's always the same..
书又不会跑
Let's go!
我们走！
I just needed to study one more paragraph.
让我把这段看完
What will you gain from studying one paragraph?
这段学完会怎样吗？
Jeetu Bhaiya said so.
拜亚哥说了
Occasional cheating is fine.
偶尔作弊是可以的
As long as you don't form a habit.
只要不养成习惯
'The person you are calling is not answering.
您拨打的电话无人接听
Please try later.'
请稍后再试”
He's not picking my call.
他不接我电话
Now he is in a happy place.
他现在在一个快乐的地方